{
  "diesel_plant": {
    "1": {
      "question": "An engine in which the fuel is burned directly within the working cylinder:",
      "choices": [
        "A. Internal combustion engine",
        "B. External combustion engine",
        "C. Compression ignition engine",
        "D. Spark ignition engine"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Internal combustion engine"
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "An engine in which the fuel is burned outside of the power cylinder.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Internal combustion engine",
        "B. External combustion engine",
        "C. Compression ignition engine",
        "D. Spark ignition engine"
      ],
      "answer": "B. External combustion engine"
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "An engine where the ignition is caused by heat of compression.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Internal combustion engine",
        "B. External combustion engine",
        "C. Compression ignition engine",
        "D. Spark ignition engine"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Compression ignition engine"
    },
    "4": {
      "question": "What temperature is required to ignite the fuel oil?",
      "choices": [
        "A. 800 to 1000F",
        "B. 700 to 900F",
        "C. 900 to 1100F",
        "D. 1000 to 1200F"
      ],
      "answer": "A. 800 to 1000F"
    },
    "5": {
      "question": "What air pressure is required to produce the required ignition temperature?",
      "choices": [
        "A. 350 to 500 psi",
        "B. 250 to 400 psi",
        "C. 450 to 600 psi",
        "D. 150 to 300 psi"
      ],
      "answer": "A. 350 to 500 psi"
    },
    "6": {
      "question": "In a four stroke Diesel engine, drawing air into the cylinder is what stroke?",
      "choices": [
        "A. First stroke",
        "B. Second stroke",
        "C. Third stroke",
        "D. Fourth stroke"
      ],
      "answer": "A. First stroke"
    },
    "7": {
      "question": "Compressing air in a four stroke cycle is",
      "choices": [
        "A. First stroke",
        "B. Second stroke",
        "C. Third stroke",
        "D. Fourth stroke"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Second stroke"
    },
    "8": {
      "question": "Which of the following strokes is produced by the burning gases:",
      "choices": [
        "A. First stroke",
        "B. Second stroke",
        "C. Third stroke",
        "D. Fourth stroke"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Third stroke"
    },
    "9": {
      "question": "Which of the following strokes expels the burned gases?",
      "choices": [
        "A. First stroke",
        "B. Second stroke",
        "C. Third stroke",
        "D. Fourth stroke"
      ],
      "answer": "D. Fourth stroke"
    },
    "10": {
      "question": "Clearing a cylinder of exhaust gases by forcing into it a current of air which provides clean air for the next compression stroke.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Scavenging",
        "B. Supercharging",
        "C. Choking",
        "D. Knocking"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Scavenging"
    },
    "11": {
      "question": "Increasing the total amount of charging air in the working cylinder of the engine.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Scavenging",
        "B. Supercharging",
        "C. Choking",
        "D. Knocking"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Supercharging"
    },
    "12": {
      "question": "The portion of the piston which extends below the piston pin and serves as a guide for the piston and connecting rod.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Piston skirt",
        "B. Piston ring",
        "C. Piston scoring",
        "D. Piston seizure"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Piston skirt"
    },
    "13": {
      "question": "Rings located in the grooves of the piston usually near the top and near the bottom.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Piston skirt",
        "B. Piston ring",
        "C. Piston scoring",
        "D. Piston seizure"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Piston ring"
    },
    "14": {
      "question": "Binding of the piston and the cylinder wall as a result of the lubrication having been destroyed by excessive temperature and friction.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Piston skirt",
        "B. Piston ring",
        "C. Piston scoring",
        "D. Piston seizure"
      ],
      "answer": "D. Piston seizure"
    },
    "15": {
      "question": "Grooves in the cylinder wall or piston or in both. It is caused by the piston scraping the cylinder wall in its movement without proper lubrication.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Piston skirt",
        "B. Piston ring",
        "C. Piston scoring",
        "D. Piston seizure"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Piston scoring"
    },
    "16": {
      "question": "A device which automatically governs or controls the speed of an engine.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Servomotor",
        "B. Governor",
        "C. Indicator",
        "D. Spectrometer"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Governor"
    },
    "17": {
      "question": "A combination of liquids which do not mix - or combine chemically.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Emulsion",
        "B. Deposition",
        "C. Evaporation",
        "D. Separation"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Emulsion"
    },
    "18": {
      "question": "What temperature should be the maximum to which lubricating oil is permitted to rise?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Not more than 100F",
        "B. Not more than 200F",
        "C. Not more than 400F",
        "D. Not more than 400F"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Not more than 100F"
    },
    "19": {
      "question": "What air pressure is needed for air starting a Diesel engine?",
      "choices": [
        "A. 250 psi",
        "B. 150 psi",
        "C. 350 psi",
        "D. 450 psi"
      ],
      "answer": "A. 250 psi"
    },
    "20": {
      "question": "At what temperature will self-igniting cartridges ignite?",
      "choices": [
        "A. About 200F",
        "B. About 100F",
        "C. About 210F",
        "D. About 250F"
      ],
      "answer": "B. About 100F"
    },
    "21": {
      "question": "The fuel is supplied by one pump and switched to each cylinder by a multi outlet rotating valve or distributor.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Distributor system",
        "B. Injector system",
        "C. Non injector system",
        "D. Non distributor system"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Distributor system"
    },
    "22": {
      "question": "This is virtually a distributor two stage pumping system that is, modified distributor system.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Distributor system",
        "B. Injector system",
        "C. Non injector system",
        "D. Non distributor system"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Injector system"
    },
    "23": {
      "question": "A chamber so proportioned with respect to the clearance volume proper of the cylinder that only about 30% of the combustion takes place within the chamber itself.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Pre combustion chamber",
        "B. Separate combustion chamber",
        "C. Ante combustion chamber",
        "D. Mixed combustion chamber"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Pre combustion chamber"
    },
    "24": {
      "question": "The entire charge is ignited in the separate combustion chamber before the initial expansion takes place, forcing the burning gases through the connecting passages and against the moving piston.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Pre combustion chamber",
        "B. Separate combustion chamber",
        "C. Ante combustion chamber",
        "D. Mixed combustion chamber"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Separate combustion chamber"
    },
    "25": {
      "question": "A chamber so designed that injection takes place directly opposite its outlet, the chamber extending backward from its outlet.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Pre combustion chamber",
        "B. Separate combustion chamber",
        "C. Ante combustion chamber",
        "D. Air cell chamber"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Ante combustion chamber"
    },
    "26": {
      "question": "Fuel is injected only into the main cylinder, during expansion of the burning gases in the main chamber, when the pressure therein drops below that of the air in the cell.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Pre combustion chamber",
        "B. Separate combustion chamber",
        "C. Ante combustion chamber",
        "D. Air cell chamber"
      ],
      "answer": "D. Air cell chamber"
    },
    "27": {
      "question": "What is the temperature of the air in the cylinder when the Diesel engine is operating at full load?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Between 800 and 1100F",
        "B. Between 800 and 1000F",
        "C. Between 900 and 1200F",
        "D. Between 900 and 1100F"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Between 800 and 1100F"
    },
    "28": {
      "question": "What are the exhaust gas temperatures at normal operating conditions?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Between 400 and 700F",
        "B. Between 500 and 800F",
        "C. Between 300 and 600F",
        "D. Between 200 and 500F"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Between 400 and 700F"
    },
    "29": {
      "question": "How are high speed Diesel engines started?",
      "choices": [
        "A. By an electric motor",
        "B. By compressed air",
        "C. By diesel fuel",
        "D. By an electric spark"
      ],
      "answer": "A. By an electric motor"
    },
    "30": {
      "question": "What speeds are considered high speed diesel engine?",
      "choices": [
        "A. 100 to 2000 rpm or 3000 rpm",
        "B. 100 to 1000 rpm",
        "C. 100 to 1500 rpm",
        "D. 100 to 1750 rpm"
      ],
      "answer": "A. 100 to 2000 rpm or 3000 rpm"
    },
    "31": {
      "question": "It is a device used for atomizing or cracking fuel oil and through which the fuel oil is injected into the working cylinders of Diesel engines.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Atomizer",
        "B. Fuel spray nozzle",
        "C. Injector",
        "D. Cracker"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Atomizer"
    },
    "32": {
      "question": "What is the proper seat width of a spray valve?",
      "choices": [
        "A. 1/16 in.",
        "B. 1/8 in.",
        "C. 1/32 in.",
        "D. 1/4 in."
      ],
      "answer": "A. 1/16 in."
    },
    "33": {
      "question": "A cylindrical vessel connected in the fuel system to absorb the shock of the injection pumps and to provide a reservoir at high pressure for supplying an even flow of fuel oil to the cylinders.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Absorber",
        "B. Accumulator",
        "C. Governor",
        "D. Injector"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Accumulator"
    },
    "34": {
      "question": "How hot are the exhaust gases?",
      "choices": [
        "A. 400 to 700F",
        "B. 300 to 500F",
        "C. 200 to 500F",
        "D. 500 to 800F"
      ],
      "answer": "A. 400 to 700F"
    },
    "35": {
      "question": "Which of the following is an automatic device used for keeping constant air pressure?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Relief valve",
        "B. Unloader",
        "C. Strainer",
        "D. Barometer"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Unloader"
    },
    "36": {
      "question": "What is the other term of the diameter of the circular cylinder?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Bore",
        "B. Stroke",
        "C. Swept volume",
        "D. Clearance"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Bore"
    },
    "37": {
      "question": "What do you call the maximum distance traveled by the piston?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Bore",
        "B. Stroke",
        "C. Swept volume",
        "D. Clearance"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Stroke"
    },
    "38": {
      "question": "Which of the following is the product of the cylinder area and stroke?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Bore",
        "B. Stroke",
        "C. Swept volume",
        "D. Clearance"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Swept volume"
    },
    "39": {
      "question": "The ratio of the clearance volume to the swept volume.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Fractional clearance",
        "B. Compression ratio",
        "C. Expansion ratio",
        "D. Cut off ratio"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Fractional clearance"
    },
    "40": {
      "question": "The piston is at maximum reach from the crankshaft to which of the following?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Top dead center",
        "B. Bottom dead center",
        "C. 他 from top center",
        "D. 他 from bottom center"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Top dead center"
    },
    "41": {
      "question": "The piston is closest to the crankshaft to which of the following?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Top dead center",
        "B. Bottom dead center",
        "C. 他 from top center",
        "D. 他 from bottom center"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Bottom dead center"
    },
    "42": {
      "question": "Which of the following engines where the expanding combustion gases act on one end of the piston?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Single acting engine",
        "B. Double acting engine",
        "C. Single expansion engine",
        "D. Double expansion engine"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Single acting engine"
    },
    "43": {
      "question": "Which of the following types of engine where the expanding combustion gases act on both ends of the piston?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Single acting engine",
        "B. Double acting engine",
        "C. Single expansion engine",
        "D. Double expansion engine"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Double acting engine"
    },
    "44": {
      "question": "The compression ratio of a Diesel engine varies from about:",
      "choices": [
        "A. 13.5 to 17.5",
        "B. 8 to 10"
      ],
      "answer": "A. 13.5 to 17.5"
    },
    "45": {
      "question": "In standard Diesel, thermal efficiency was not much higher than about what percent?",
      "choices": [
        "A. 35%",
        "B. 30%",
        "C. 40%",
        "D. 50%"
      ],
      "answer": "A. 35%"
    },
    "46": {
      "question": "A closed heat exchanger that transfers heat from compressed air to cooler air.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Regenerator",
        "B. Intercooler",
        "C. Aftercooler",
        "D. Reheater"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Aftercooler"
    },
    "47": {
      "question": "Which of the following is used to improve cold weather starting?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Poppet valve",
        "B. Glow plug",
        "C. Check valve",
        "D. Spark plug"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Glow plug"
    },
    "48": {
      "question": "The rated power that the manufacturer claims the engine is able to provide on a continuous basis without incurring damage.",
      "choices": [
        "A. Brakepower",
        "B. Continuous duty rating",
        "C. Intermittent rating",
        "D. Power rating"
      ],
      "answer": "B. Continuous duty rating"
    },
    "49": {
      "question": "What is the peak power rating that can be produced on an occasional basis?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Brakepower",
        "B. Continuous duty rating",
        "C. Intermittent rating",
        "D. Power rating"
      ],
      "answer": "C. Intermittent rating"
    },
    "50": {
      "question": "Which of the following is the value of a property that includes the effect of friction?",
      "choices": [
        "A. Brake value",
        "B. Friction value",
        "C. Indicated value",
        "D. Actual value"
      ],
      "answer": "A. Brake value"
    }
  }
}